var questions = [{
    "question": "Name one of the five books in the Bible that contain only one chapter ?",
    "option1": "1 John",
    "option2": "Titus",
    "option3": "Obadiah",
    "option4": "Habakkuk",
    "answer": "3"
},{
    "question": "What did King Solomon ask God to give him?",
    "option1": "Prosperity",
    "option2": "Money",
    "option3": "Fame",
    "option4": "Wisdom",
    "answer": "4"
},{
    "question": "How many days was Jonah in the belly of the big fish?",
    "option1": "One Day",
    "option2": "Five Days",
    "option3": "Three Days",
    "option4": "Ten Days",
    "answer": "3"
},{
    "question": "How many times does the Bible mention the word “SNOW?”",
    "option1": "24 Times",
    "option2": "5 Times",
    "option3": "Never",
    "option4": "12 Times",
    "answer": "1"
},{
    "question": "How many days and nights did Jesus fast?",
    "option1": "22",
    "option2": "40",
    "option3": "365",
    "option4": "12",
    "answer": "2"
},{
    "question": "Where did Jesus grow up after returning from Egypt?",
    "option1": "Jerusalem",
    "option2": "Bethlehem",
    "option3": "Nazareth",
    "option4": "Lower East Side",
    "answer": "3"
},{
    "question": "What piece of clothing made Joseph’s brothers jealous?",
    "option1": "Shoes",
    "option2": "Belt",
    "option3": "Headpiece",
    "option4": "Coat",
    "answer": "4"
},{
    "question": "How was Ruth related to Naomi?",
    "option1": "Sister",
    "option2": "Daughter",
    "option3": "Daughter-in-law",
    "option4": "Cousin",
    "answer": "3"
},{
    "question": "What were the names of the twins who wrestled in their mother’s womb?",
    "option1": "Jacob and Esau",
    "option2": "Paul and Peter",
    "option3": "Cain and Abel",
    "option4": "Jesus and John",
    "answer": "1"
},{
    "question": "What does this name of God mean: Jehovah Rapha?",
    "option1": "The Lord who provides",
    "option2": "The Lord who heals",
    "option3": "The Lord who sends",
    "option4": "The Lord who leads",
    "answer": "2"
}]